These are the correct values.
هذه هي القيم الصحيحة.
Our first expression is true because all of these conditions are separated by
عبارتنا الأولى هي true، لأن جميع هذه الحالات مفصولة باستخدام عوامل تشغيل OR،
ORs which means only one of them must be true for this whole combination to be true.
ما يعني أنه يجب أن تكون إحداها true لتكون هذه التوليفة بأكملها true.
And the first condition,
والحالة الأولى،
a equals a, is true.
a == a، هي true.
Our next expression is false because with an AND operator,
تعبيرنا الثاني false، لأنه بوجود عامل تشغيل AND،
both of it's combined conditions need to be true for the whole combination to be true.
يجب أن تكون كلتا حالتيه المشتركتين true لتكون التوليفة بأكملها true.
And is three greater than five is false.
وقيمة 5 &lt; 3 هي false.
So that means this whole expression is false as well.
هذا يعني أن هذا التعبير بأكمله هو false أيضاً.
Our third expression is a little tricky.
تعبيرنا الثالث صعب قليلاً.
First, Java sees what's in the parentheses.
أول ما يراه Java هو ما في القوسين.
Here are two comparisons combined with an or.
هاتان مقارنتان مدموجتان باستخدام OR.
And that means that only one of these comparisons has to be
ويعني هذا أنه على واحدة فقط من هاتين المقارنتين أن تكون true
true for this combination to also be true.
لتكون هذه التوليفة true أيضاً.
We know that three greater than five is false,
نعرف أن 5 &lt; 3 هي false،
but two less than 10 is true.
لكن 10 &gt; 2 هي true.
And that means that this or combination is also true.
ما يعني أن توليفة OR هذه هي أيضاً true.
And then this value is combined with another true with an AND operator,
ثم يتم جمع هذه القيمة مع true آخر وعامل تشغيل AND،
and an and combination is true when both of its side conditions are true.
وتوليفة AND تكون true عندما يكون كلا جانبيها true.
So this whole expression is true.
فهذا التعبير بأكمله هو true.
Our last expression checks if not,
يتفقد تعبيرنا الأخير
10 is greater than one.
ليس (1 &lt; 10).
We know that 10 greater than one is true,
نعلم أن 1 &lt; 10 هي true،
and then are NOT operator negates this value.
ثم يلغي عامل التشغيل NOT، "ليس"، هذه القيمة.
So this whole thing turns into not true which is to say, false.
لذا يتغير هذا كله إلى not true، "ليس صواب"، وهو false بتعبير أخر.
So logical operators let you combine
إذن، تسمح لك عوامل التشغيل المنطقية
multiple test conditions and negate values when you want to.
بجمع حالات اختبار متعددة ونفي قيم عندما تريد ذلك.